<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather Forecast</string>
    <string name="title_city">City</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="update_database">Update database</string>

    <string-array name="cities">
        <item> Amur </item>
        <item> Arkhangelsk </item>    
        <item> Astrakhan </item>        
        <item> Belgorod </item>        
        <item> Bryansk </item>        
        <item> Vladimir </item>        
        <item> Volgograd </item>        
        <item> Vologda </item>        
        <item> Voronezh </item>        
        <item> Ivanovo </item>        
        <item> Irkutsk </item>        
        <item> Kaliningrad </item>        
        <item> Kamchatka </item>        
        <item> Kemerovo </item>        
        <item> Krasnodar </item>        
        <item> Krasnoyarsk </item>        
        <item> Kursk </item>        
        <item> St. Petersburg </item>        
        <item> Lipetsk </item>        
        <item> Magadan </item>        
        <item> Moscow </item>        
        <item> Murmansk </item>        
        <item> Novosibirsk </item>        
        <item> Omsk </item>        
        <item> Orenburg </item>        
        <item> Penza </item>        
        <item> Primorsk </item>        
        <item> Pskov </item>        
        <item> Rostov on Don </item>        
        <item> Ryazan </item>        
        <item> Samara </item>        
        <item> Saratov </item>        
        <item> North Ossetia </item>        
        <item> Smolensk </item>        
        <item> Stavropol </item>        
        <item> Taganrog </item>        
        <item> Tambov </item>        
        <item> Tomsk </item>        
        <item> Tula </item>        
        <item> Tyumen </item>        
        <item> Ulyanovsk </item>        
        <item> Khabarovsk </item>        
        <item> Khanty-Mansiysk </item>        
        <item> Chelyabinsk </item>        
        <item> Yaroslavl </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="update_cities">
        <item>Amur, RU</item>
        <item>Arkhangelsk, RU</item>    
        <item>Astrakhan, RU</item>        
        <item>Belgorod, RU</item>        
        <item>Bryansk, RU</item>        
        <item>Vladimir, RU</item>        
        <item>Volgograd, RU</item>        
        <item>Vologda, RU</item>        
        <item>Voronezh, RU</item>        
        <item>Ivanovo, RU</item>        
        <item>Irkutsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Kaliningrad, RU</item>        
        <item>Kamchatka, RU</item>        
        <item>Kemerovo, RU</item>        
        <item>Krasnodar, RU</item>        
        <item>Krasnoyarsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Kursk, RU</item>        
        <item>Saint Petersburg, RU</item>        
        <item>Lipetsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Magadan, RU</item>        
        <item>Moscow, RU</item>        
        <item>Murmansk, RU</item>        
        <item>Novosibirsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Omsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Orenburg, RU</item>        
        <item>Penza, RU</item>        
        <item>Primorsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Pskov, RU</item>        
        <item>Rostov-on-Don, RU</item>        
        <item>Ryazan, RU</item>        
        <item>Samara, RU</item>        
        <item>Saratov, RU</item>        
        <item>North Ossetia, RU</item>        
        <item>Smolensk, RU</item>        
        <item>Stavropol, RU</item>        
        <item>Taganrog, RU</item>        
        <item>Tambov, RU</item>        
        <item>Tomsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Tula, RU</item>        
        <item>Tyumen, RU</item>        
        <item>Ulyanovsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Khabarovsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Khanty-Mansiysk, RU</item>        
        <item>Chelyabinsk, RU</item>        
        <item>Yaroslavl, RU</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descr_city">
         <item> Amursk is a city in Russia, the administrative center of the Amur region of the Khabarovsk Territory.
Amursk was founded on June 19, 1958. The city is located in the northeast
Middle Amur Lowland, on the left bank of the Amur,
more precisely, at the intersection of its left-bank channels of the Old Amur, Padalinskaya, Galbona and Sandinskaya,
in 328 km to the north from Khabarovsk, 45 km to the south from Komsomolsk-on-Amur. In fact, his industrial satellite.
The city is stretched along the Sandinskaya canal for 14 km and consists of two almost equal areas.
        </item>
                
        <item> Arkhangelsk is a city in the north of the European part of Russia.
Administrative center of Arkhangelsk region and Primorsky municipal district.
The city of regional importance, forms a municipal formation the city of Arkhangelsk with the status of the city district.
Population: 351,488 [3] people (2017). The largest city among the regions
Northern European Russia (Arkhangelsk, Murmansk, Vologda regions, Komi republics and Karelia).
Founded by the decree of Ivan the Terrible in 1584 near the St. Michael's Archangel Monastery (hence the name of the city)
        </item>
                
        <item> Astrakhan is a city in Russia, the administrative center of the Astrakhan region.
The oldest economic and cultural center of the Lower Volga region and the Caspian Sea.
It is included in the list of historical cities of Russia.
It is a city of regional importance. Forms the city district of the city of Astrakhan.
        </item>
                
        <item> Belgorod (historic Belgorod Russian, Belaya Vezha, Sarkel) is a city in the south of the middle section of the European part of Russia,
administrative center of the Belgorod region. Located on the southern outskirts
Central Russian Upland, on the banks of the Belgorod Reservoir, the rivers Vezelki and Seversky Donets,
700 km south of Moscow, 40 km from the border with Ukraine.
Forms a municipal formation city district Belgorod. Population 391 135 [2] people (2017).
        </item>
                
        <item> Bryansk is a city in the Russian Federation, an administrative center
Bryansk region; city ​​of regional importance, forms a municipal
education city of Bryansk with the status of the city district.
Located on the western edge of the Central Russian Upland, both
the banks of the Desna River at the confluence of Bolva and Sněžeti into it. Population - 406 553 [1] people. (2017).
        </item>
                
        <item> Vladimir is a city in Russia, the administrative center of the Vladimir region and the city district of Vladimir.
In the XII-XIV centuries - the capital of the Grand Duchy of Vladimir.
One of the largest tourist centers in the European part of Russia.
It is part of the Golden Ring of Russia. The population is 356 168 people. (2017).
        </item>
                
        <item> Volgograd is a city in the southeast of the European part of the Russian Federation with a population of 1 015 586 people (2017).
The administrative center of the Volgograd region. Until 1925 it was called Tsaritsyn, from 1925 to 1961 - Stalingrad.
Hero-city, the place of the Battle of Stalingrad. Forms the city district of Volgograd.
        </item>
                
        <item> Vologda is a city in Russia, administrative, cultural, transport and scientific center
            Vologda region, the center of the Vologda region, which is not included, having the status
            city ​​of regional importance and forming the city district municipal formation "City
            Vologda. "
        </item>

        4213/5000
        <item>Vorónezh — gorod v Rossii, administrativnyy tsentr Voronezhskoy oblasti.
Raspolozhen na beregakh Voronezhskogo vodokhranilishcha, reki Voronezh, v 8,5 kilometrakh ot
vpadeniya yeyo v reku Don, ot Moskvy — 463 km.
Naseleniye goroda Voronezha — 1 039 801[2] chel. (2017).
</item>
        <item>Ivánovo (v 1871—1932 godakh — Ivánovo-Voznesénsk) — gorod (s 1871 goda)
v Rossii na beregu reki Uvod', administrativnyy tsentr Ivanovskoy oblasti,
nadelon statusom gorodskogo okruga. Naseleniye — 406 933[2] chel. (2017).
</item>
        <item>Irkútsk — gorod v Rossii, administrativnyy tsentr Irkutskoy oblasti i
Irkutskogo rayona, obrazuyet gorodskoy okrug gorod Irkutsk.
Shestoy po velichine gorod Sibiri s chislennost'yu naseleniya 623 736[2] chel. (2017).
V predelakh Irkutskoy aglomeratsii na 2016 god prozhivayet 1,1 mln chelovek.
</item>
        <item>Kaliningrád, do 4 iyulya 1946 goda — Konigsberg (nem. Königsberg), takzhe Korolevets
(pol'sk. Królewiec, lit. Karaliaučius, do 1255 goda — Tvangste) — gorod v Rossii,
administrativnyy tsentr Kaliningradskoy oblasti. Samyy zapadnyy oblastnoy tsentr strany.
Raspolozhen pri vpadenii reki Pregoli v Kaliningradskiy zaliv. Naseleniye — 467 289[2] chel. (2017).
</item>
        <item>Kamchátka — poluostrov v severo-vostochnoy chasti Yevrazii na territorii Rossii.
Omyvayetsya s zapada Okhotskim morem, s vostoka —
Beringovym morem i Tikhim okeanom.
Poluostrov vytyanut s severa na yug na 1200 km.
Soyedinyayetsya s materikom uzkim (do 93 km) peresheykom — Parapol'skim dolom. Naibol'shaya shirina
(do 440 km) — na shirote mysa Kronotskiy.
Obshchaya ploshchad' poluostrova ~ 270 tys. km².
</item>
        <item>Kémerovo — gorod v Rossii, administrativnyy tsentr Kemerovskoy oblasti. V nastoyashcheye vremya zanimayet tridtsatoye mesto
po chislennosti naseleniya i pyatidesyatoye po ploshchadi sredi gorodov Rossii.
Raspolozhen na yuge Zapadnoy Sibiri, na oboikh beregakh rek Tomi i Iskitimki, v severnoy chasti Kuznetskogo ugol'nogo basseyna (Kuzbassa).
Kemerovo — vazhnyy administrativnyy, ekonomicheskiy, nauchnyy, kul'turnyy, transportnyy i promyshlennyy tsentr Sibiri.
Kemerovo — pervyy[6] po chislennosti naseleniya gorod v Kemerovskoy oblasti i plotnosti naseleniya.
Gorod yavlyayetsya tsentrom Kemerovskoy aglomeratsii. Naseleniye — 556 920[2] chel. (2017).
</item>
        <item>Krasnodár (do 1920 goda — Yekaterinodár) — gorod na yuge Rossii, raspolozhennyy na
pravom beregu reki Kubani, na rasstoyanii 120—150 kilometrov k vostoku ot Chornogo i
Azovskogo morey, i 1350 km (po shosse) k yugu ot Moskvy.</item>
        <item>Krasnoyársk (proiznosheniye (inf.)) — odin iz krupneyshikh gorodov Rossii, kul'turnyy, ekonomicheskiy,
promyshlennyy i obrazovatel'nyy tsentr Tsentral'noy i Vostochnoy Sibiri.
Administrativnyy tsentr Krasnoyarskogo kraya (vtorogo po ploshchadi sub"yekta
Rossii) i gorodskogo okruga gorod Krasnoyarsk. Tsentr Vostochno-Sibirskogo ekonomicheskogo rayona.
Osnovannyy v 1628 godu, yavlyayetsya krupneyshim iz starinnykh gorodov Sibiri. Vo vremena «zolotoy
likhoradki» dolgoye vremya byl krupnym protsvetayushchim kupecheskim tsentrom Sibiri. Samyy vostochnyy gorod-millioner v Rossii.
Gorod raspolozhen v tsentre Rossii, na oboikh beregakh Yeniseya na styke Zapadnosibirskoy ravniny,
Srednesibirskogo ploskogor'ya i Sayanskikh gor v ushchel'ye,
obrazovannom samymi severnymi otrogami Vostochnogo Sayana.
Naseleniye goroda — 1 082 933[3] (2017). V Krasnoyarskoy aglomeratsii prozhivayet boleye polutora millionov zhiteley.
</item>
        <item>Kursk — gorod v Rossii, administrativnyy tsentr Kurskoy oblasti, a takzhe
Kurskogo rayona. V sostav rayona ne vkhodit, yavlyayas' gorodom oblastnogo znacheniya,
obrazuyushchim munitsipal'noye obrazovaniye gorod Kursk so statusom gorodskogo okruga.
</item>
        <item>Sankt-Peterbúrg (s 18 avgusta 1914 goda do 26 yanvarya 1924 goda — Petrográd, s 26
yanvarya 1924 goda do 6 sentyabrya 1991 goda — Leningrád) — vtoroy po chislennosti
naseleniya gorod Rossii. Gorod federal'nogo znacheniya. Administrativnyy tsentr
Severo-Zapadnogo federal'nogo okruga i Leningradskoy oblasti. Osnovan 16 (27) maya 1703
goda Petrom I. V 1712—1918 godakh stolitsa Rossiyskogo gosudarstva.</item>
        <item>
        Lipetsk is a city (since 1779) in Russia, the administrative center of the Lipetsk region.
        It is the core of the largest Russian agglomeration with a specialization in the field of ferrous metallurgy of the full cycle,
        industrial, agrotechnological and aviation center, resort. The population is 510 439 people. (2017).
        The distance to Moscow is 450 km, to Voronezh - 132 km.
                </item>
            
    <item> Magadan is a port city in the northeast of Russia.
        The administrative center of the Magadan Region,
        forms a municipal formation "the city of Magadan".
        Population - 92 711 people. (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Moscow (pronunciation (inf.)) - the capital of the Russian Federation, the city of the federal
                    values, the administrative center of the Central Federal District and the center of the Moscow
                    area, which does not include. The largest city in the population of Russia
                    and its subject - 12,500,123 people. (2018), the most populated of the cities, completely
                    located in Europe, is among the top ten cities in the world in terms of population.
                    Center of the Moscow city agglomeration. </item>
            
    <item> Murmansk [3] (kild Murman Lann, before 1917 - Romanov-on-Murman) -
        a city in the north-west of Russia,
        administrative center of the Murmansk region.
        Population - 298,096 [2] people (2017).
        Murmansk is the largest city in the world, located behind the
        The Arctic Circle.
        Murmansk is located on the rocky eastern coast of the Kola Bay of the Barents Sea.
        One of the largest ports of Russia.
                </item>
            
    <item> Novosibirsk (pronunciation (inf.), until 1925 - Novo-Nikolaevsk) - the third largest
        population of the city of Russia,
        has the status of an urban district.
        The administrative center of the Siberian Federal District,
        Novosibirsk Region and the Novosibirsk Region that is part of it;
        the city is the center of the Novosibirsk agglomeration. The largest trade, business, cultural,
        industrial, transport and scientific center of Siberia.
        Novosibirsk was founded in 1893, the status of the city was received in 1903.
        The population is 1 602 915 people. (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Omsk is one of the largest cities in Russia, located at the confluence of the Irtysh and Om rivers,
        a large scientific, cultural, sports and industrial center. City of Labor Glory.
        The city with a million population (1,178,391 [3] people in 2017), the second largest in terms of population in
        Siberia and the eighth in Russia. Large transport hub:
        from west to east through the city passes the railway Trans-Siberian Railway,
        and from the south to the north - the navigable river Irtysh.
                </item>
            
    <item> Orenburg (from 1938 to 1957 - Chkalov) is a city in Russia.
        The administrative center of the Orenburg region.
        Forms the city district of the city of Orenburg.
                </item>
            
    <item> Penza is a city (since 1663), located on the Volga Upland in the center of the European part of Russia,
        administrative, economic and cultural center of the Penza region (since 1939).
        It is a city of regional importance, forms a municipal formation city district of Penza [5].
        Population - 523,726 [1] people (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Primorsk (until 1948 Koivisto, finnish Koivisto, from koivu, birch,
        Bereza, Berezovsky, Bjorke from the Swedes were also called in the past. Björkö - a birch island) - a city (since 1940)
        in Russia, in the Vyborgsky District of the Leningrad Region.
        The city is located on the shore of the Gulf of Finland, 75 km from St. Petersburg and 48 km from Vyborg.
        The population is 5739 people. (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Pskov is a city (since 903 [5] [6]) in the north-west of Russia,
        the administrative center of the Pskov region and the Pskov district, forming the city district of Pskov.
        Located on the river Velikaya at the confluence of it with the river Pskov.
        The population of the city is 209,840 [4] people. (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Rostov-on-Don is the largest city in the south of the Russian Federation, administrative
                    center of the Southern Federal District and the Rostov Region. City of military glory (2008).
                    It is based on the reading and writing of Empress Elizabeth Petrovna from December 15, 1749. Located
                    in the southeast of the East European Plain, on the banks of the Don River, 46 km from its place
                    the confluence of the Azov Sea, 1092 km south of Moscow. </item>
            
    <item> Ryazan (pronunciation (inf.)) (until 1778 - Pereyaslavl-Ryazan) is a city in Russia,
        administrative center of the Ryazan region. It is one of the thirty largest cities in Russia.
        Population - 537 622 [2] people (2017).
                </item>
            
    <item> Samara is a city in the Middle Volga region of Russia,
        center of the Volga region economic region and the Samara region, forms the city district of Samara.
        City of Labor and Military Glory (2016).
        Population - 1 169 719 [2] people (2017),
        the ninth largest city in Russia. Within the agglomeration
        (the third largest population in Russia) is home to over 2.7 million people.
                </item>
    <item> Saratov is a city in the southeast of the European part of Russia,
        the administrative center of the Saratov region and the Saratov region,
        which is not included, being a city of regional importance,
        forms a municipal entity in the city of Saratov with the status of a city district.
        A major cultural, economic and educational center of the Volga region.
        It is among the twenty largest cities in Russia, not being a millionaire city,
        at the same time is the center of the Saratov agglomeration, whose population exceeds 1.2 million people.
                </item>
            
    <item> The Republic of North Ossetia-Alania (the republic of Central Asia, Ististon-Alani as sounds (inf.);
        short title: North Ossetia) - a subject of the Russian Federation [7], a republic in its composition.
        It is part of the North Caucasus Federal District and is part of the
        North Caucasus economic region.
                </item>
            
    <item> Smolensk is a city in central Russia, an administrative, industrial and cultural center of the Smolensk region.
        This is one of the oldest cities in Russia (the first chronicle mentions refers to the year 863).
        He wears the title of "Hero City" (since May 6, 1985),
        was awarded the Order of Lenin and the Order of the Patriotic War of the 1st degree, the medal "Gold Star".
                </item>
            
    <item> Stavropol (from Greek σταυρός - "cross", πόλις - "city") - city [5],
        administrative center of the Stavropol Territory of the Russian Federation. Cultural,
        business and industrial (mechanical engineering, instrumentation) center of the province.
        One of the largest cities in the North Caucasus and the North Caucasus Federal District.
                </item>
            
    <item> Taganrog is a city in the Rostov region, a port on the shore of the Azov Sea (on the coast
                    Taganrog Bay, 70 km from the regional center of the city of Rostov-on-Don), forms
                    municipal formation "City of Taganrog" with the status of city district.
                    It was founded by Peter the Great in 1698. Taganrog became the first naval base of Russia,
                    the first Russian port on the open sea coast and the first city in Russia,
                    built according to the regular plan. It is included in the list of historical settlements of Russia.
                    The population is 250 287 people. (2017). About one hundred nationalities live in Taganrog.
                    The largest diasporas are Greek, Jewish and Armenian.
                    November 3, 2011 the city was awarded the honorary title "City of Military Glory", and in December
                    2015, the Bank of Russia in a series of coins "City of Military Glory" issued a coin,
                    dedicated to Taganrog. May 8, 2015, the grand opening of the stele "City
                    military glory. "</item>
            
    <item> Tambov is a city in Russia, administrative, economic and cultural center of Tambov region, is
        also administrative center of Tambov district, which itself does not enter, being
        administrative-territorial unit of the city of regional importance, forming the same name
        municipal formation city district city Tambov.
        Located in the central part of the Oka-Don plain on the channel of the Tsna River, 480 km south of Moscow.
        The population is 290 365 people. (2017), and the population density is 3101 people / km².
                </item>
            
    <item> Tula is a city in Russia, the administrative center of the Tula region and the urban district of the city of Tula.
        Hero City (since 1976).
        Tula is located in the north of the Central Russian Upland on the bank of the Upa River in 193 km to the south of Moscow.
        The length of the city from north to south is 30 km, from west to east - 25 km.
                </item>
            
    <item> Tyumen is a city in Russia, an administrative center of the Tyumen region and Tyumen district,
        in which structure does not enter. Forms the city district of Tyumen.
        It occupies the 18th place among the cities of Russia in terms of population.
        The first Russian city in Siberia [6] [7].
                </item>
            
    <item> Ulyanovsk (in 1648-1780 - Sinbirsk, in 1780-1924 - Simbirsk) - a city in the European part of Russia,
        administrative center of the Ulyanovsk region. It is a city of regional significance,
        forms a municipal formation in the city of Ulyanovsk with the status of a city district.
        Located on the Volga Upland, on the banks of the Volga River (Kuibyshev Reservoir) and
        Sviyaga, at the point of rapprochement of their channels.
        It is located 890 km to the east / southeast of Moscow.
        Population: 624 518 people. (2017) (22nd place in the Russian Federation).
                </item>
            
    <item> Khabarovsk is a city (since 1880) in Russia, the administrative center of the Far Eastern Federal District
        Russia and the Khabarovsk Territory.
        One of the largest political, educational and cultural centers of the Russian Far East.
        The population is 616 242 people. (2017). The area of ​​the city is 386 km ².
                </item>
    <item> Khanty-Mansiysk (Khanty Yomvosh, Yomvҷ, Mansa Abga) is a city in Russia,
        the administrative center of the Khanty-Mansiysk Autonomous Okrug - Ugra and the municipal district of the same name.
        The largest of the centers of the autonomous regions of Russia and the only one of them whose population
        exceeds 90,000 people (including the centers of the united autonomous okrugs). </item>
            
    <item> Chelyabinsk (pronunciation (inf.)) - the seventh by the number of inhabitants, the fourteenth for
                    the city of the Russian Federation, the administrative center of Chelyabinsk
                    region, urban district with intra-urban division. Population - 1 198 858 people
                    (2017). Chelyabinsk is located on the geological boundary of the Urals and Siberia, on the eastern
                    slope of the Ural Mountains, along both banks of the Miass River (Tobol basin). </item>
            
    <item> Yaroslavl is a city in Russia, the administrative center of the Yaroslavl region. Population - 608,079 [2] people (2017).
        Yaroslavl is the third largest city in the Central Federal District of the Russian Federation.
        The city is a transport hub from which railways and motorways diverge in the direction of Moscow, Vologda, Rybinsk,
        Kostroma, Ivanova and Kirov. In Yaroslavl, there are also a river port and an airport. The area of ​​the city is 205.8 km ². </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="temperature">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-5</item>
        <item>-5</item>
        <item>-10</item>
        <item>-10</item>
        <item>+5</item>
        <item>+5</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-15</item>
        <item>-5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="windSpeed">
        <item>2.6</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pressure">
        <item>767</item>
        <item>760</item>
        <item>767</item>
        <item>770</item>
        <item>767</item>
        <item>767</item>
        <item>762</item>
        <item>763</item>
        <item>765</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>764</item>
        <item>765</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="humidity">
        <item>87</item>
        <item>90</item>
        <item>87</item>
        <item>76</item>
        <item>87</item>
        <item>79</item>
        <item>67</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>82</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="type_weather">
        <item>Cloudy</item>
        <item>Rainy</item>
        <item>Snowy</item>
        <item>Hot</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Cloudy</item>
        <item>Rainy</item>
        <item>Snowy</item>
        <item>Hot</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
        <item>Clear</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descr_weather">
        <item>Cloudy weather</item>
        <item>Rainy weather</item>
        <item>Snowy weather</item>
        <item>Hot weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Cloudy weather</item>
        <item>Rainy weather</item>
        <item>Snowy weather</item>
        <item>Hot weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
        <item>Clear weather</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city_path_image">
        <item> amur </item>
        <item> arkhangelsk </item>    
        <item> astrakhan </item>        
        <item> belgorod </item>        
        <item> briansk </item>        
        <item> vladimir </item>        
        <item> volgograd </item>        
        <item> vologda </item>        
        <item> voronezh </item>        
        <item> ivanovo </item>        
        <item> irkutsk </item>        
        <item> kaliningrad </item>        
        <item> kamchatka </item>        
        <item> kemerovo </item>        
        <item> krasnodar </item>        
        <item> krasnoyarsk </item>        
        <item> kursk </item>        
        <item>saintpetersburg</item>      
        <item> lipetsk </item>        
        <item> magadan </item>        
        <item> moscow </item>        
        <item> murmansk </item>        
        <item> novosibirsk </item>        
        <item> omsk </item>        
        <item> orenburg </item>        
        <item> penza </item>        
        <item> primorsk </item>        
        <item> pskov </item>        
        <item>rostovondon</item>    
        <item> ryazan </item>        
        <item> samara </item>        
        <item> saratov </item>        
        <item> northossetia </item>        
        <item> smolensk </item>        
        <item> stavropol </item>        
        <item> taganrog </item>        
        <item> tambov </item>        
        <item> tomsk </item>        
        <item> tula </item>        
        <item> tyumen </item>        
        <item> ulyanovsk </item>        
        <item> habarovsk </item>        
        <item> khantymansiysk </item>        
        <item> chelyabinsk </item>        
        <item> yaroslavl </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>
    <string name="file_saved">File saved!</string>
    <string name="city_show">City :  </string>
    <string name="temp_show">Temperature :  </string>
    <string name="wind_speed_show">Wind speed :  </string>
    <string name="pressure_show">Pressure :  </string>
    <string name="humidity_show">Humidity :  </string>
    <string name="db_updated">Database updated!</string>
</resources>